omniref.com 2016-04-16

# Omniref

Last updated: December 23, 2015

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you or associated with you (“personal information”) is collected and used by Omniref (“Omniref”, “we”, or “us”), and the choices we offer you to access, update and control it. This policy applies to the online services offered by Omniref at omniref.com (the “Website”, “Service”, or “Services”).

### Personally Idenfitying Information

You can browse our site without providing personal information, but you must create an account in order to access some of the features of our site. When you create an account, we may collect personal information, such as your email address, user name, password, location and birthdate. We may also collect information from you in order to service a paid account, such as your billing address and payment information.

### Cookies

We automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our Website or use our Services. When you visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Services (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us to track your usage of the Services over time. 

Cookies are required to use the Website. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If your do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly.

### Anonymous Information

We may collect log file information from your browser or mobile device each time you access the Services. Log file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, internet protocol address, browser type, identity of your internet service provider, information about your mobile device, referring / exit pages and URLs, the number and duration of page views, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Website, domain names, landing pages, and other such information. 

When you access our site through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique identification number associated with your device and other device information. We may also employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service. 

We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Service.

### How We Use Collected Information

We use the information we gather to operate, maintain, and provide our features and services, including but not limited to:

  * remembering information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site.
  * customizing your user experience.
  * providing and monitoring the effectiveness of our Services.
  * monitoring aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on our website and our Services.
  * diagnosing or fixing technology problems.
  * otherwise to plan for, improve and enhance our Services.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Omniref is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Omniref will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Marketing Communications

If you are a registered user of our Services, we may occasionally send you email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with the Website. If you do not want to receive promotional emails from us, you can click the 'unsubscribe' link on promotional email communications. 

Note that you will not be able to unsubscribe or opt-out of non-promotional messages regarding your account, such as account verification, password reminders, changes or updates to features of the Services, or technical and security notices.

### Do Not Track

At this time, we do not collect information from you for behavioral advertising purposes, though we may collect persistent identifiers from your browser or mobile device to assist us with providing and improving the Services. Because we collect browsing and persistent identifier data only for analytic and internal purposes, your selection of the 'Do Not Track' option provided by your mobile browser will not have any effect on our collection of analytics information or the collection of a persistent identifier.

### Data Storage

Omniref uses third-party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Service. Although Omniref owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Omniref application, you retain all rights to your data. 

### Security

We work hard to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of personal or financial information. All such electronic information is stored on restricted database servers, trasferred via enctypted connections, and is generally kept until such time as you may ask us to edit or delete it. We only disclose such information to our employees, agents or affiliates that a) need to know that information in order to process it for us or to provide other services, and b) have agreed not to disclose it to others.

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches, no website or internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or other breach will never occur. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

### Children's Privacy

This Website is not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from children under 13, we will delete or anonymize such information. Please contact us at support@omniref.com if you have any questions about children's privacy.

### Changes to this Policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may occasionally need to change this policy. If we do update it, we’ll notify you by posting the new policy on this page, updating the 'Last Revision' date above, and emailing you the changes or a link to the modified document.

### Your Acceptance of these Terms

By using the Service, you signify your acceptance of this policy and the terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@omniref.com](mailto:support@omniref.com)
